commoncraft.com 2009-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Common Craft Store | Common Craft - Explanations In Plain English

At Common Craft, we are committed to protecting your privacy. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself.  To provide certain services that you request and to optimize your ability to use this site, we sometimes need to collect and/or pass along information, and this agreement sets forth the conditions for your use of those services and explains our data collection and use practices.

**1\. Common Craft Services.** At Common Craft we are committed to making your total experience a positive one. Upon entering your information and the request for which you would like a video, we will provide you with a list of possible videos that may meet your needs, if any.  We can not guarantee that any video will meet your particular needs, nor can we guarantee the accuracy or content of any video.  Common Craft Videos are intended to provide entertaining and cursory education with regard to the subject matter thereof.  Any health, financial, or other decision you may make relating to the subject matter of a Video should be made on the basis of subsequent research and evaluation by you or trained professionals on your behalf.

**2.     Collection of Personal Information.**  We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are purchasing a video or asking for specific information.  If you ever want to review or update the information we have stored for you, simply send an email to [store@commoncraft.com](mailto:store@commoncraft.com) and we will send you your profile to allow you to edit your personal information. We will ask for sufficient identification to assure that only you can access your profile.  
**  
3.     Use of your Personal Information. ** We may work with other companies to provide services at your request or on our behalf, including download or delivery of videos.  Common Craft may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Common Craft or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Common Craft and its web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Common Craft, its web sites, or the public.  By providing information to us, or by submitting a service request, you expressly consent to be bound by this Privacy Policy and our Content License Agreement.    
**  
4.     Use of Cookies. ** To ensure we are publishing content customers need and want, Common Craft collects site-visitation statistics using cookies. We use this information in aggregated form for site-visitation statistics for improving our site.  We also use this information to help assure that you receive accurate information regarding our products and services.  When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customerâ€™s machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously.  Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, or action tags, assist in delivering the cookie. This technology tells us how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on the 1ratemtg.com web page. We do not use this technology to access your personally identifiable information; it is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about site usage. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies but do not allow other companies to place clear gifs on our sites.  If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from our site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site.

**5.     Third Party Links.**  Common Craft may provide links from our web site to third party web sites. We encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information.  We have no control over the content, privacy protection practices, or other aspects of any linked site.   
**  
6.     General Provisions. **  
**a.     Changes to this Statement. ** Common Craft will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date in the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, Common Craft will notify you by placing prominent notice on the web site.  
**b.     Contact Information.**  Common Craft welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us by e-mail, or postal mail. 

Common Craft Privacy Department  
3411 Hunter Blvd. South  
Seattle, WA 98144

Last Updated: Sunday, August 31, 2008
